

PROFILE

I have 4 year's experience in customer service and electrical and energy systems. I have found my interactions with customers to be the most fulfilling. I enjoy trouble shooting with them, and talking them through their new systems.

I am seeking a new career opportunity where can I grow my customer service skills in an environment that promotes diversity, teamwork, and continuous learning.

CONTACT

Phone: 440-832-0068

Email: jackhmartin.98@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Classic Movie Marathons Gaming Cooking

JACK MARTIN

EDUCATION

Cuyahoga Valley Career Center

September 2014 – June 2016 Electrical and Energy Systems Program

WORK EXPERIENCE

Life Safety Systems (Service technician)

December 2018 - April 2020

Performing annual fire alarm inspections and taking detailed notes on deficiencies found during the inspection. Calling customers and fire departments to set up fire alarm inspections, installing additions, and programing fire alarm panels.

Mikes Computer Rescue

January 2021- Current

Repairing Hardware, software, and logic issues with many computers. As well as checking in customers and performing on site work.

Securitec One (installation technician)

June 2016 - December 2017

Installing and programming Security systems, fire alarm, and camera systems for Aldi.

SKILLS

- Ability to adjust my communication style to match the customer's needs
- Strong desire to help people
- Effective decision making
- Strong understanding of technical and system issues and ability to apply this knowledge to problem solving
- Experience in team mentoring and support to create maximum effectiveness and team cohesiveness
- Understanding and usability of Microsoft products
- Desire to learn on the job